https://www.iqphoto.com/privacy-policy

Home Work
Specialties
City Hall Info
Contact Us
Rome WeddingPrivate Estate WeddingSan Francisco Indoor WeddingBridal SessionBotanical GardensBackyard WeddingSF City Hall WeddingIntimate Indian WeddingCasual Outdoor WeddingWine Country WeddingTuscany WeddingRitz Carlton SF WeddingNorcal Ranch WeddingSF City Hall Wedding IIFairmont SF WeddingSantorini WeddingCabo San Lucas WeddingIndoor Hotel SF WeddingIntimate SF WeddingHistoric SF Club WeddingMaui WeddingThailand WeddingSilverado Resort WeddingFairmont SF Wedding IIBlog Style Weddings
Proposals Engagements City Hall 4KLGBT WeddingsIcelandMuir WoodsRetouchingIndian WeddingsLivestreamShort FilmsFamily PortraitsCorporateVideoCOVID WeddingsAnniversaryMain City Hall PageHow To... (Official Guide)Grand StaircaseThe RotundaMayors BalconyCity Hall 4th FloorCounty Clerk OfficeCeremony Vows (official)Packed City HallNatural LightFront DoorEvening WeddingsCity Hall 3rd floorCandids PhotosCOVID AlternativesBest HotelsWhat to do afterHow to (Lifehack)Capturing EternityGeneral AdvisesAudris HAnahita SNikki KScott CJon TStacie TJack NKang HKathleen HLeslie LIris KVictoria GJamena PChris SEric LBrinn PAaron FHannah DReg TVictoria GIrene CKrishni AButch MNicole GTina KAndrea FNick FEmily ACarmela GFiona JDonald CSarah VAndy CChristian KGrace LJennie MStephanie PYingzi CBrianna RMatt RManuel NTim CDouglas KEric FJulia AMaggie CEugene BSandra PBurlington WBob MJenny WLena GAndrew GTonya SMichelle NHilaria SEleonora RWeiwei ZCynthia JTina RBrinn PGalina GPam THeather PMegan MNaomi SErica GJennie MJason TDiane TSandy SMary MDavid RMark KAyu HElizabeth BNydia HIgor MAnnette SCindy TShelley LQing Qing BAlicia GHossanah LWilliam RTimothy CErika DAlex EBecca LKellee PSarah HComprehensive Reviews
Professionalism
Creativity
Technical Skills
Personality
Approach
Help & Support
Overall Experience
Efficiency
Topic: City Hall
Camera Shy
Expertise Value
Fun Club Reviews
Reviews Safe Open Venues Elopement Guide COVID-19 Thoughts Our FAQ Published Work City Hall
Idea Boards Albums For Photographers
Detailed Reviews
Last updated: April 25, 2019Wedding Photography by IQphoto (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the San Francisco Wedding Photography by IQphoto website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.iqphoto.com/blogInformation Collection And UseWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:NameEmail addressTelephone numberLog DataWe collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.Compliance With LawsWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.TERMS AND CONDITIONS
Work
Specialties
City Hall
Info
Contact Us
